SACHIN KUMAR MEENA

Full Stack Developer

Summary

I am a person of creative skills, aiming high in life to achieve my goals. The objectives are very clear - To set goals and to achieve them with respect. My creative and motivation skills give me an edge over others. Talking about my area of interest is, Web & App Development pertaining which I have wrapped up projects using Asp.net, PHP, NodeJs, React and UX/UI projects. Apart from this, I have taken projects in Android and Java conjointly. I have a knowledge of Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop. Worked with many project teams to create user-friendly and appealing application interfaces and websites for users.

Experiences

Dec 2016 - Sep 2017	Poornima Foundation, Jaipur ERP Developer
May 2017 - Aug 2017	SunShine Softwares, Jaipur Android Application Development Trainee
May 2016 - Sep 2016	Poornima Group of Colleges, Jaipur Laravel Application Development Trainee

Projects

Nov 2016 - Jan 2017	Yourdreamstores.com, Europe Web & UX / UI Designer
Oct 2016 - Nov 2016	Dr.LisaHunt, USA web Designer & Developer
Jan 2016 - April 2016	Know Your Student, PIET Jaipur Team Leader & Developer

Personal Info

DOB

March 23, 1996

Address

Meena Ki Dhani, Mandoli, Sikar, Rajasthan, 302022

Phone

+91 - 9694280191

Email

sachinmeena.dev@gmail.com

Website

sachinmeena.online

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/sachinmeena

Facebook

facebook.com/sachinmeena.dev

Father's Name

Sh. Rohitashva Meena

Mother's Name

Smt. Saroj Meena

Skills & Education

Professional Skills

HTML 5 / CSS 3

Java Script
PHP / Java
Server & Database
Mobile Application
Photoshop / Illustrator

Personal Skills

Creativity
Leadership
Organization
Dedication

Education

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Engineering
 Poornima Institute of Engineering & Technology
 Rajasthan Technical University, Kota
 Senior Secondary (P C M)
 Kendriya Vidhalaya, Durg (C. G.)
 Central Board of Secondary Education
 Secondary
 St. Michael HS, Kanker (C. G.)
 Chahattisgarh Board of Secondary Education

Hobby

Producing EDM, Mentoring, Photography, Exploring new research ideas.